Ford Foundation records, Office of Communications, Production, Art and Design, Photographs and Negatives, Office Files of Laura Walworth and Dayna Bealy FA1819
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Office Files of Dayna Bealy, 1997-2000; 2; 9.4 Cubic Feet 22 containers
  - 1212 - Annual Report 1998, Bay Area Video Coalition, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC) - Arts Stabilization, Andy Freeberg, photographer (Box 19, Folder 213)
    4 contact sheets, 6 5x7 black and white prints
  - 1213 - Annual Report 1998, Access Support and Advancement Program (ASAP), Strive, Assets/Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), 1998 Highlights, James Hamilton, photographer (Box 19, Folder 214)
    10 contact sheets, 4 5x7 black and white prints
  - 1213 - Annual Report 1998, Access Support and Advancement Program (ASAP), Strive, Assets/Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), 1998 Highlights, James Hamilton, photographer - negatives (Box 28, Folder 369)
  - 1214 - Annual Report 1998, Metro Industrial Areas Foundation, Peace Social Justice (PSJ)/Civil Society, James Hamilton, photographer (Box 19, Folder 215)
    6 contact sheets, 4 black and white prints
  - 1214 - Annual Report 1998, Metro Industrial Areas Foundation, Peace Social Justice (PSJ)/Civil Society, James Hamilton, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 370)
  - 1215 - Annual Report 1998, Education Fund for Family Plan Council New York, Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Care Services, James Hamilton, photographer (Box 19, Folder 216)
    1 contact sheet, 1 black and white print
  - 1215 - Annual Report 1998, Education Fund for Family Plan Council New York, Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Care Services, James Hamilton, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 371)
  - 1216 - Annual Report 1998, Assets/Community Development Field, Camden Development Collaborative Revitalization Effort, New Jersey, James Hamilton, photographer (Box 19, Folder 217)
    3 contact sheets, 4 black and white prints
  - 1216 - Annual Report 1998, Assets/Community Development Field, Camden Development Collaborative Revitalization Effort, New Jersey, James Hamilton, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 372)
  - 1217 - Annual Report 1998, Enterprise Corps of Delta, Mississippi, Fundees - Delta Pride Laundry in Clarksdale and Unique Charter, Assets/Economic Development (Box 19, Folder 218)
    10 contact sheets, 2 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1217 - Annual Report 1998, Enterprise Corps of Delta, Mississippi, Fundees - Delta Pride Laundry in Clarksdale and Unique Charter, Assets/Economic Development - negatives (Box 29, Folder 373)
  - 1218 - Annual Report 1998, Assets/Community Development Field, Arizona Community Foundation, Gentle Rain Products on the Hope Reservation, Dan Hunting, photographer (Box 19, Folder 219)
  - 1218 - Annual Report 1998, Assets/Community Development Field, Arizona Community Foundation, Gentle Rain Products on the Hope Reservation, Dan Hunting, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 374)
  - 1219 - Annual Report 1998, Self-Help Ventures Fund, Assets/Individual Asset Development, Nancy Pierce, photographer (Box 19, Folder 220, Box 20, Folder 221)
    6 8x10, and 120 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1219 - Annual Report 1998, Self-Help Ventures Fund, Assets/Individual Asset Development, Nancy Pierce, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 375)
  - 1220 - Annual Report 1998, Women's Self-Employment Project in Chicago (WSEP), Assets/Individual Asset Development, Michael L. Abramson, photographer (Box 20, Folder 222)
    4 contact sheets, 2 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1221 - Njabulo Ndebele, Scholar in Residence at the Ford Foundation, Steven Freeman, photographer, undated (Box 20, Folder 223)
    8 black and white contact sheets, 2 5x7 prints
  - 1221 - Njabulo Ndebele, Scholar in Residence at the Ford Foundation, Steven Freeman, photographer - negatives, undated (Box 29, Folder 376)
  - 1222 - Annual Report 1998, National Partnership for Women and Families, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights/Promoting Equal Opportunity, Tony Arruza, photographer (Box 20, Folder 224)
    4 black and white contact sheets, 5 8x10 prints
  - 1222 - Annual Report 1998, National Partnership for Women and Families, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights/Promoting Equal Opportunity, Tony Arruza, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 377)
  - 1223 - Annual Report 1998, Community Foundation South Carolina, Assets/Community Development, Peter Frank Edwards, photographer (Box 20, Folder 225)
    12 black and white contact sheets, 3 8x10 prints
  - 1223 - Annual Report 1998, Community Foundation South Carolina, Assets/Community Development, Peter Frank Edwards, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 378)
  - 1224A - Annual Report 1998, College of Agriculture and Forestry, Vietnam, National University in Ho Chi Minh City, Assets/Community and Resource Development (CRD) (Box 20, Folder 226)
    1 8x10 print
  - 1224B - Vietnam, Ministry of Culture and Information, Performing Arts Department (985-0663), Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC), 1998 November (Box 20, Folder 227)
  - 1224C - Vietnam National University, Hanoi (980-0228-1), Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Education, Knowledge, and Religion (EKR), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 228)
    5 5x7 black and white prints
  - 1224D - Ho Chi Minh City Fine Arts Museum (975-1760), Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC), 1998 (Box 20, Folder 229)
    3 8x10 prints
  - 1225A - Annual Report 1998, Association of Young Leaders, Russia, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Civil Society (Box 20, Folder 230)
  - 1225B - Annual Report 1998, Anna (985-0487), Russia, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights (Box 20, Folder 231)
    1 5x7 black and white print
  - 1225C - Annual Report 1998, Women's Public Association "FEMINA," Russia, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC) (Box 20, Folder 232)
    1 8x10 black and white print
  - 1225D - Annual Report 1998, Citizens Foundation (970-0443), Russia Field Office, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Civil Society (Box 20, Folder 233)
  - 1225E - Annual Report 1998, Mothers' Rights Fund (09700443), Russia Field Office, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights (Box 20, Folder 234)
  - 1226A - Annual Report 1998, Museum Trustees of Kenya, Assets/Community and Resource Development (CRD), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 20, Folder 235)
    4 black and white contact sheets, 2 8x10 prints
  - 1226A - Annual Report 1998, Museum Trustees of Kenya, Assets/Community and Resource Development (CRD), Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 379)
  - 1226B - Annual Report 1998, Makerere University, Kenya, Assets/Community and Resource Development (CRD), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 20, Folder 236)
    3 black and white contact sheets, 2 8x10 prints
  - 1226B - Annual Report 1998, Makerere University, Kenya, Assets/Community and Resource Development (CRD), Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 380)
  - 1226C - Annual Report 1998, Kenya Society of the Physically Handicapped, Kenya, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 20, Folder 237)
    2 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 print
  - 1226C - Annual Report 1998, Kenya Society of the Physically Handicapped, Kenya, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 381)
  - 1226D - Annual Report 1998, African Medical and Research Foundation, Kenya, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 20, Folder 238)
    1 contact sheet
  - 1226D - Annual Report 1998, African Medical and Research Foundation, Kenya, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 382)
  - 1226E - Annual Report 1998, Law Development Centre, Kenya, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 20, Folder 239)
  - 1226E - Annual Report 1998, Law Development Centre, Kenya, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 383)
  - 1226F - Annual Report 1998, Straight Talk Foundation, Kenya, Assets/Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 20, Folder 240)
    3 black and white contact sheets, 5 8x10 prints
  - 1226F - Annual Report 1998, Straight Talk Foundation, Kenya, Assets/Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 384)
  - 1226G - Annual Report 1998, Family Planning Private Sector, Kibera Slum, Nairobi, Kenya, Assets/Community and Resource Development (CRD) and Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 20, Folder 241)
    2 contact sheets, 3 8x10 prints
  - 1226H - Annual Report 1998, Mathare Youth Sports Organization, Kenya, Assets, Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 20, Folder 242)
    1 black and white contact sheet, 1 5x7 print
  - 1226H - Annual Report 1998, Mathare Youth Sports Organization, Kenya, Assets, Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC), Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 385)
  - 1226I - Annual Report 1998, Samburu Girl Child Education Support Programme, Kenya, Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH)/Community Involvement, Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 20, Folder 243)
    2 black and white contact sheets, 2 8x10 prints
  - 1226I - Annual Report 1998, Samburu Girl Child Education Support Programme, Kenya, Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH)/Community Involvement, Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 386-387)
  - 1226J - Annual Report 1998, Kuona Trust, Kenya, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 20, Folder 244)
    3 black and white contact sheets, 6 8x10 prints
  - 1226K - Annual Report 1998, African Foundation Learning Group, Dandora, Kenya, Assets/Peace and Social Justice (PSJ), Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 21, Folder 245)
    3 black and white contact sheets and 3 prints
  - 1226K - Annual Report 1998, African Foundation Learning Group, Dandora, Kenya, Assets/Peace and Social Justice (PSJ), Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 388)
  - 1227A - Annual Report 1998, Woman and Memory Forum, Cairo, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC)/Governance and Community Service (GCS), Trygve Bolstad, photographer (Box 21, Folder 246)
    1 contact sheets, 3 8x10 prints
  - 1227B - Annual Report 1998, Friends of the Environment and Development Association, Cairo, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC), Trygve Bolstad, photographer (Box 21, Folder 247)
    4 black and white contact sheets, 3 8x10 prints
  - 1227C - Annual Report 1998, Desert Development Project, American University in Cairo, Rural Poverty and Resources/Assets, Trygve Bolstad, photographer (Box 21, Folder 248)
    5 contact sheets, 4 prints
  - 1227D - Annual Report 1998, International Islamic Center for Population Studies and Research, Cairo, Assets/Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH) and Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), Trygve Bolstad (Box 21, Folder 249)
    3 contact sheets, 7 prints
  - 1227E - Annual Report 1998, The Cultural Association Sweden-Egypt, Al Tanboura Musicians in Port Said, (985-1845), Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC), Trygve Bolstad, photographer (Box 21, Folder 250)
    2 black and white contact sheets, 4 8x10 prints
  - 1228 - Annual Report 1998, Interfaith Education Fund/Project Quest, Assets/Workforce Development, John Dyer, photographer (Box 21, Folder 251)
    5 black and white contact sheets, 10 8x10 prints
  - 1228 - Annual Report 1998, Interfaith Education Fund/Project Quest, Assets/Workforce Development, John Dyer, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 389)
  - 1229A - Annual Report 1998, RIWAQ, Center for Architectural Conservation, West Bank, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC), Rula Halawani, photographer (Box 21, Folder 252)
    3 contact sheets
  - 1229A - Annual Report 1998, RIWAQ, Center for Architectural Conservation, West Bank, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Media, Arts, and Culture (MAC), Rula Halawani, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 390)
  - 1229B - Annual Report 1998, Palestinian Academic Society for the Study of International Affairs (PASSIA), West Bank, Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), Peace and Security, International Studies, Rula Halawani, photographer (Box 21, Folder 253)
    3 contact sheets, 4 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1229B - Annual Report 1998, Palestinian Academic Society for the Study of International Affairs (PASSIA), West Bank, Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), Peace and Security, International Studies, Rula Halawani, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 391)
  - 1229C - Annual Report 1998, Palestinian Agricultural Relief Committee, Assets/Community and Resource Development (CRD), West Bank, Rula Halawani, photographer (Box 21, Folder 254)
    2 contact sheets and 3 black and white 8x10 prints
  - 1229D - Annual Report 1998, Al-Ma'mal Foundation, West Bank, Possible ID, Rula Halawani, photographer (Box 21, Folder 255)
    1 contact sheet, 8 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1229D - Annual Report 1998, Al-Ma'mal Foundation, West Bank, Possible ID, Rula Halawani, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 393)
  - 1229D - Annual Report 1998, Al-Ma'mal Foundation, West Bank, Possible ID - 1) Sireen, 2.) Marwan, 3.) Marwan, Photos Taken by Kids in Program, 3 1/4 inch floppy disk (Box 21, Folder 255)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
  - 1229D - Annual Report 1998, Al-Ma'mal Foundation, West Bank, Possible ID - 4) Wafa, 5) Loay, 6) Hiba, Photos Taken by Kids in Program, 3 1/4 inch floppy disk (Box 21, Folder 255)
  - 1229 - Annual Report 1998, West Bank, Rula Halawani, photographer (Box 21, Folder 256)
    3 contact sheets, 5 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1229 - Annual Report 1998, West Bank, Rula Halawani, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 394)
    Restricted - Preservation concerns
  - 1230 - Annual Report 1998 - Chile Field Office (Not Divided by Grantee), Chile and Peru, Rhodri Jones/Panos, photographer (Box 21, Folder 257)
    16 contact sheets
  - 1230A - Annual Report 1998, Chile Field Office, EPES/Evangelical Lutheran Church in Chile, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Governance and Civil Society (GCS), Rhodri Jones/Panos, photographer (Box 21, Folder 258)
    7 black and white contact sheets, 3 8x10 prints
  - 1230B - Annual Report 1998, Chile Information Project Environmental Project, Government and Civil Society/Civic Participation, Rhodri Jones/Panos, photographer (Box 21, Folder 259)
    1 contact sheet, 2 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1230C - Annual Report 1998, Corporation for the Legal Training for Citizenship and Democracy, Chile, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC)/Governance and Civil Society (GCS), Rhodri Jones, photographer (Box 21, Folder 260)
    4 contact sheets, 1 8x10 print
  - 1230D - Annual Report 1998, Chile Field Office, TERRAM/Fundación para la Promocion del Desarrollo Sustentable, Governance and Civil Society (GCS), Rhodri Jones/Panos, photographer (Box 21, Folder 261)
    3 contact sheets, 2 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1230E - Annual Report 1998, Pontifical Catholic University of Peru, 960-1016, Governance and Civil Society (GCS)/Education, Knowledge, Religion (EKR), Rhodri Jones/Panos, photographer (Box 22, Folder 262)
  - 1230F - Annual Report 1998, DEMUS/Office for the Defense of the Rights of Women, Chile Field Office, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC)/Assets, Rhodri Jones/Panos, photographer (Box 22, Folder 263)
    4 contact sheets, 3 black and white 8x10 prints
  - 1230G - Annual Report 1998, COPEME/NGO Consortium for the Promotion of Small and Micro Enterprises, ASSETS/Economic Revitalization, 940-0751, Rhodri Jones/Panos, photographer (Box 22, Folder 264)
    5 contact sheets, 8 8x10 black and white prints
  - Sustainable Solutions: Building Assets for Empowerment and Sustainable Development, Ford Foundation publication, undated (Box 22, Folder 265)
  - 1231A - Annual Report 1998, Juan Diego Foundation, 980-0710, Mexico, Assets ED, Pierce Benatar/Panos, photographer (Box 22, Folder 267)
    5 black and white contact sheets, 2 8x10 prints
  - 1231B - Annual Report 1998, CIMAC - Communication and Information for Women, 980-0690, Assets/Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH)/Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights and International Cooperation (HRIC), Pierce Benatar, photographer (Box 22, Folder 268)
    10 black and white contact sheets, 10 8x10 prints
  - 1231C - Annual Report 1998, Mexican Center for Philanthropy, 980-0785, Peace and Social Justice/Governance and Civil Society (GCS), Pierce Benatar, photographer (Box 22, Folder 269)
    3 black and white contact sheets, 3 8x10 prints
  - 1231D - Annual Report 1998, College of the Southern Border (Ecosur), Mexico, Assets, Human Development and Reproductive Health (HDRH) and Community and Resource Devemopment (CRD), Pierce Benatar/Panos (Box 22, Folder 270)
    12 black and white contact sheets, 10 prints
  - Agenda for Photography Sessions for Piers Benatar, Mexico Office, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 271)
  - 1273 - Annual Report 1999, Single Gender Academics, Johns Hopkins University, Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC), Education Reform, Tony Gonzalez, photographer (Box 22, Folder 272)
    8 black and white contact sheets, 9 8x10 black and white prints
  - 1274 - Annual Report 1999, LISC Neighborhood/Franchise Project/Assets/Development Finance and Economic Security, Andre Lambertson, photographer (Box 22, Folder 273)
    8 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 print, 10 5x7 prints
  - 1274 - Annual Report 1999, LISC Neighborhood/Franchise Project/Assets/Development Finance and Economic Security, Andre Lambertson, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 395)
  - 1275 - Annual Report 1999, Center for Governmental Studies, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Civil Society, Robert Yager, photographer (Box 22, Folder 274)
    5 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 print, 12 5x7 prints
  - 1275 - Annual Report 1999, Center for Governmental Studies, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Civil Society, Robert Yager, photographer - negatives (Box 29, Folder 396)
  - 1276 - Annual Report 1999, Rainforest Alliance/Smartwood, Assets/Environment and Development, Stella Johnson, photographer (Box 22, Folder 275)
    10 black and white contact sheets, 6 8x10 prints, 7 5x7 prints
  - 1276 - Annual Report 1999, Rainforest Alliance/Smartwood, Assets/Environment and Development, Stella Johnson, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 397)
  - 1277 - Annual Report 1999, Michigan Neighborhood Partners, Assets/Community Development, George Waldman, photographer (Box 23, Folder 276)
    Grant 09801657
    4 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 print, 12 5x7 prints
  - 1278 - Annual Report 1999, Reinvestment Fund (DVCRF), Assets/Development and Finance and Economic Security, Harvey Finkle, photographer (Box 23, Folder 277)
  - 1279 - Annual Report 1999, Twin Cities Rise, Assets/Workforce Development, Steve Woit, photographer (Box 23, Folder 278)
    3 black and white contact sheets, 6 4x6 prints
  - 1279 - Annual Report 1999, Twin Cities Rise, Assets/Workforce Development, Steve Woit, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 398)
  - 1280 - Annual Report 1999, Kentucky Highlands Investment Corporation, Assets/Development and Finance and Economic Security, John Sommers II, photographer (Box 23, Folder 279)
    Grant 09901114
    11 black and white contact sheets, 10 4x6 prints
  - 1281 - Ford Foundation - Trinational Reception, Tony Gonzalez, photographer, 1999 October 21 (Box 23, Folder 280)
  - 1282 - Project GRAD, National Convening at Ford Foundation, Tony Gonzalez, photographer, 1999 November 2 (Box 23, Folder 281)
    Grant 09700169
    1 black and white contact sheet
  - 1283 - Annual Report 1999, Immigration Law Enforcement Project (ILEMP), Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights, Susan Gaetz, photographer (Box 23, Folder 282)
    6 black and white contact sheets, 4 8x10 prints
  - 1284 - Annual Report 1999, Public Private Ventures, Seattle LATTERS Program, Assets/Workforce Development, Dan Lamont, photographer (Box 23, Folder 283)
  - 1285 - Annual Report 1999, Pioneer Human Services, Assets/Workforce Development, Dan Lamont, photographer (Box 23, Folder 284)
    6 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 print, 6 4x6 prints
  - 1286A - Annual Report 1999, South Africa Makuleke Communal Property Association, 9951425, Assets/Environment and Development, Tswaledi Thobgane, photographer (Box 23, Folder 285)
    10 black and white contact sheets, 7 4x6 black and white prints
  - 1286A - Annual Report 1999, South Africa Makuleke Communal Property Association, 9951425, Assets/Environment and Development, Tswaledi Thobgane, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 399)
  - 1286B - Annual Report 1999, South Africa Tshwarang Legal Advocacy Center to End Violence Vs. Women, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights, Tswaledi Thobgane, photographer (Box 23, Folder 286)
    2 color contact sheets
  - 1286B - Annual Report 1999, South Africa Tshwarang Legal Advocacy Center to End Violence Vs. Women, Peace and Social Justice (PSJ)/Human Rights, Tswaledi Thobgane, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 400)
  - 1286C - Annual Report 1999, South Africa Joint Education Trust (JET), Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Higher Education, Tswaledi Thobgane, photographer (Box 23, Folder 287)
    Grant 980-1697
    10 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 print, and 4 4x6 prints
  - 1286C - Annual Report 1999, South Africa Joint Education Trust (JET), Education, Media, Arts, and Culture (EMAC)/Higher Education, Tswaledi Thobgane, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 401)
  - 1287 - Winter 2000/Womens Issue, India Violence Story, David Wells, photographer (Box 23, Folder 288)
  - 1288 - Annual Report 1999, Jobs for the Future, Assets/Workforce Development, George Waldman, photographer (Box 23, Folder 289)
    Grant 09701396
    2 black and white contact sheets, 3 8x10 prints
  - 1289A - Annual Report 1999, Kenya, Women Fighting AIDS in Kenya, Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Health, Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 23, Folder 290)
  - 1289A - Annual Report 1999, Kenya, Women Fighting AIDS in Kenya, Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Health, Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 402)
    Grant 09901381
  - 1289B - Annual Report 1999 - Kenya, Family Planning Private Sector, Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Health, Wendy Stone, photographer (Box 23, Folder 292)
    2 black and white contact sheets, 1 8x10 print, 4x6 prints
  - 1289B - Annual Report 1999 - Kenya, Family Planning Private Sector, Assets/Sexual and Reproductive Health, Wendy Stone, photographer - negatives (Box 30, Folder 403)